viigo.com 2007-12-15

# Privacy Policy

Virtual Reach Inc. (“Virtual Reach”), along with its affiliates and the various trade names under which it operates and provides the products and services, is committed to protecting your online privacy while providing you with the most useful and enjoyable wireless Internet experience possible. While you can use many features of Virtual Reach products anonymously, you are required to provide personal information to gain access to some of our premium content and services. 

This Privacy Policy is also part of our Terms of Service.

### How we collect and use personal information

Registering for any subscription with Virtual Reach involves the collection of personal information to complete the license agreement. Virtual Reach will require your name, address, e-mail address, city and country, and may require other contact information. With your approval, we occasionally will send e-mail to notify you about important changes to the services, and special offers from us and select Virtual Reach partners. If you would rather not receive these e-mail notifications, you can simply indicate that preference either when you register or at any time you modify your account. 

If you enter a contest or respond to a promotion, we may ask for your postal address so we can notify contest winners and deliver promotional items and services. When you enter this information, we will save it in your subscription profile so that you won’t have to enter it again. We occasionally may also send you postal mail to notify you about important changes to the site, new services, and special offers from us and select Virtual Reach partners. If you would rather not receive such information via postal mail, you can indicate this when you enter your address or you can modify your account at any time to indicate your preference.

### How we protect your personal information

All personal data you enter on Virtual Reach is encrypted with secure server software (SSL) that encodes the information before your Web browser software sends it to us. The SSL software decodes the data only after it reaches our server, meaning hackers will not be able to access any of your personal information while it is in transit. Once the data reaches our site, the same state-of-the-art security software we use to guard all of our company’s essential business data protects your personal data as well. 

In addition to using the most secure technology available, we work tirelessly to make sure that we use any information you provide us only in ways you have approved. We send you only the e-mail you have approved in your account information or on your e-mail subscription sign-up page.

### How we use "cookies"

As you probably know, "cookies" are small pieces of information that some Web sites store on your computer's hard drive when you visit them. Like many other Web sites, Virtual Reach uses cookies to identify users so they don’t have to enter a user ID and password upon each visit. Most Web browsers automatically accept cookies but allow you to modify security settings so you can approve or reject cookies on a case-by-case basis. 

### What we provide to third parties

While Virtual Reach does not provide any third-party access to your personal information except to facilitate your own attempts to register with our partners or receive offers from select partners as mentioned elsewhere in this policy, we may provide third parties with aggregate statistics about our customers, traffic patterns, and related site information. This data reflects usage patterns gathered from our servers each month, but it does not contain behavioral or identifying information about any individual subscription unless that user has given us permission to share that information. Any information provided in this regard will always be subject to valid and binding confidentiality agreements with third parties. 

Virtual Reach may also provide to third parties any information or data related to individual subscriptions as required by law, whether pursuant to a warrant for investigative purposes or a court order, or the like.

### License Subscriptions

Our site uses an order form for customers to subscribe and purchase our products and services. We collect subscribers’ billing and financial information (such as their account or credit card numbers). Financial information that is collected is used only to bill the user for products and services. This information is used only for that purpose and is never shared with any other person or company. We do use a third party to process credit cards. We don't store credit card information for any use other than processing the credit card transactions. 

Our store maintains a list of receipts or Order History for each customer. This information is accessible by logging in to the store and then clicking on the Order History link located in the right margin of the Lobby page or at the top of your Shopping Cart page. This information is for your convenience. It is not available to anyone else. Your credit card information is not stored in your Order History.

### Links

This site contains links to other sites. The products and services provided by Virtual Reach contain access through RSS feeds to information and content provided by publishers and parties other than Virtual Reach. Virtual Reach is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of any Web site other than its own. Moreover, Virtual Reach is not responsible for any violations of privacy resulting from accessing any of the RSS feeds within its products and services. As privacy practices may be different at other sites and provisions of content, please review each site's privacy statement. 

### Obtaining your consent

By using our products and services, you give Virtual Reach permission to collect information about you as an anonymous user for the purpose of calculating aggregate statistics. If you register at Virtual Reach, you authorize Virtual Reach to use information you provide to personalize the information we deliver to you and to use your demographic information when calculating aggregate customer data. As a registered subscriber, you give Virtual Reach and our agents permission to send you e-mails related to the subscription e-mail services to which you subscribe. 

If you are under the age of 18, you must not provide your name, e-mail address, or any other identifying information without the consent of your parent or guardian, or as otherwise provided for by applicable law.

Any changes to our privacy policy will be posted on this page so that you are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances we disclose it.

### Tell us what you think

Virtual Reach welcomes your questions and comments about our privacy policy.
